const quizData = {
    "풍풍이" : [
    {
        question : " First question ~",
        photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
        options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
        answer : "options3"
    },
    
    {
        question : " question 2 ~",
        photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
        options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
        answer : "2번"
    },
    
    {
        question : " question 3 ~",
        photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
        options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
        answer : "3번"
    },
    
    {
        question : "question 4~",
        photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
        options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
        answer : "4번"
    },

    {
        question : " Final question ~",
        photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
        options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
        answer : "5번"
    }
    ],

    "바마" : [
        {
            question : " First question ~",
            photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
            options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
            answer : "options3"
        },
        
        {
            question : " question 2 ~",
            photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
            options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
            answer : "2번"
        },
        
        {
            question : " question 3 ~",
            photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
            options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
            answer : "options3"
        },
        
        {
            question : " question4 ~",
            photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
            options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
            answer : "4번"
        },
    
        {
            question : " Final question ~",
            photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
            options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
            answer : "5번"
        }
        ],
        "흥부와 놀부" : [
            {
                question : " First question ~",
                photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
                options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
                answer : "3번"
            },
            
            {
                question : " question 2 ~",
                photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
                options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
                answer : "2번"
            },
            
            {
                question : " question 3 ~",
                photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
                options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
                answer : "3번"
            },
            
            {
                question : " question4 ~",
                photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
                options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
                answer : "4번"
            },
        
            {
                question : " Final question ~",
                photo : "/images/fungfung/fung1.avif",
                options : ["1번","2번","3번","4번","5번"],
                answer : "5번"
            }
        ]

};

export default quizData;